iamwire.com 2016-06-09

# Privacy Policy | iamwire

As used in this Privacy Policy, “iamwire” refers to all websites (including iamwire.com, and ire.iamwire.com.

By visiting iamwire, viewing our content or research, attending or viewing any of our events or programs and/or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**What Types of User Information Does iamwire Obtain?**

iamwire may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device (“Information”), which may include information that can be used to identify you as specified below (“Personally Identifiable Information”):

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Mailing Address
  * Telephone Number(s)
  * Blog or Website URL
  * Photo
  * Demographic Information (e.g., age, gender, interests, and preferences)
  * Professional Title
  * Company
  * Industry
  * Activities or Content Viewed on iamwire
  * Information Collected Automatically

In certain cases, we may request that you provide some of the Information identified above in order to obtain specific products or services (such as registering for a iamwire event or logging in to download a research report from iamwire). If you choose not to provide the Information we request, you may still use iamwire, but you may be unable to access certain features or services.

When you register to receive any products or services from iamwire or provide information to iamwire in any other manner, you agree to provide only true, accurate, current and complete information.

**Information Collected Automatically**

iamwire may automatically receive and log certain types of information when you visit or interact with our websites, services, mobile applications or other products, including:

  * Browser Information
  * Operating System Information
  * Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)
  * IP Address
  * Internet Service Provider
  * Content Viewed
  * Geographic Location
  * Connection Speed
  * Time of Visit
  * Referring Site, Application, or Service
  * Registration Time

**How Do We Use This Information?**

We use the Information we obtain from or concerning you or your computer or device to provide iamwire products and services, fulfill your requests, improve our products and services, personalize and tailor your experience on iamwire, operate our business, and understand how users are engaging with iamwire.

In addition, we may use Information from or concerning you or your computer or device to facilitate the delivery of content or advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you about new or existing products and services or special offers. For example, we may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to our products and services to the email address associated with your account.

**iamwire’s Use of Cookies**

iamwire may place “cookies” on your computer or device that may contain anonymous Information that is associated with you. Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize users, and are typically placed on your hard disk by a web server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain (here, iamwire) that issued the cookie to you or that, in some cases, can be read by a third party domain.

Our cookies may record Information about your use of iamwire so that we can provide a continuous and more personalized experience for you, including for one or more of the following purposes: to help identify visitors; assess usage patterns; identify preferences; control the display of ads; diagnose problems with our servers; gather demographic information; analyze trends and usage patterns; conduct research; deliver editorial content; record registration and personalized information; and otherwise administer iamwire products and services.

If you do not wish to have iamwire place and use cookies on your computer, you should set your browser preferences to refuse cookies before accessing iamwire. iamwire is not responsible for any failure by you or your browser to accurately implement or communicate your browser preferences or settings. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of iamwire that depend on cookies.

**iamwire does not control and is not responsible for the use of cookies by its third party partners or advertisers**.

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

iamwire may disclose Information (including Personally Identifying Information) from or concerning you or your computer or device to third parties in the circumstances described below. By visiting, accessing, attending or using iamwire’s products, services or events, you consent to the disclosure of your Information to certain categories of third parties in the manner described below. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the policies or practices of any of these third parties.

**Service Providers**

iamwire relies on third party vendors and service providers to provide support and assistance for its products, services and events (“Service Providers”), and we may disclose your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to these Service Providers to the extent necessary to support our products, services or events, or as otherwise set forth below.

**Event Registration**

iamwire uses third parties, such as Meraevents and Explara, to process registration for iamwire events and programs. iamwire may provide your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to such registration services when you register for a iamwire event or program. In addition, as discussed below, iamwire (or its third party registration service) may provide your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to companies that sponsor or underwrite portions of an event that you register for, attend, or view.

**Web Hosts**

iamwire’s website services are hosted by Gogrid, an enterprise web hosting platform. All Information obtained and stored by iamwire’s websites  processed and stored on servers that are owned and operated by WordPress.

**Third Party Websites**

iamwire offers the ability to share iamwire content on Third Party Websites, including social networking and blogging services such as LinkedIn or Facebook, through “plugins” or “widgets” (such as LinkedIn’s “in” button or Facebook’s “Like” button). When you elect to share content and information with others on Third Party Websites, iamwire may transmit your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to such Third Party Websites. This Information may be visible on the Third Party Website to anyone who has access to that content or Information. Your decision to share information in this manner is completely voluntary. You should ensure that you are comfortable with how Third Party Websites may share your Information by reviewing their privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy settings directly on those Third Party Websites.

**URL/Referrer Header Information**

When you visit iamwire websites, certain information about the content or activities you have engaged in on iamwire may be reflected in the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) for the page you are viewing on iamwire (i.e., the Internet “address,” commonly displayed in the browser window). For example, the date or title of an article you are viewing may appear in the URL for that page. In addition, if you are logged into a iamwire account, certain account information (may be visible in the URL when you visit your account on iamwire. If you leave iamwire to visit a third party website, including when you click on an advertisement or link or when you share information through a social plug-in (like the Linked In “in” button), the information contained in the URL may be transmitted to the third party website by your browser.

**Advertisers and Analytics Services**

iamwire uses third party advertisers, including ad networks, to provide advertising on its websites. In addition, as discussed in (“Analytics Services”), iamwire uses third party analytics products to obtain information about how users are using and interacting with iamwire. These third parties may receive Information (including Personally Identifying Information) from iamwire as discussed in greater detail in (“Security and Protection of Personally Identifying Information”).

**Law Enforcement/Legal Process**

We may disclose your Information (including Personally Identifying Information) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to comply with any law, regulation or legal request; enforce, apply, or investigate breaches of our terms of use and other agreements; respond to public requests; or protect the rights, property, user experience or safety of iamwire, our employees, our users, or others. This can include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Comments and Public Posts; Sharing on Third-Party Websites**

iamwire encourages active participation by users, including through comments on iamwire. However, please be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Information, personal or otherwise, on iamwire, that Information can be viewed, collected and used by others, including other users, search engines, advertisers, third party applications developers, and anyone with access to iamwire. iamwire has no control over the use, collection or disclosure of any Information that you post publicly on iamwire.

**Change of Control**

If iamwire, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by another company or party, user Information will be one of the assets transferred or acquired by the purchaser. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any purchaser of iamwire or its assets may continue to collect, use and disclose your Information as set forth in this Policy.

**Third-Party Advertising on iamwire**

iamwire may allow third party advertising serving companies, including ad networks (“Advertisers”), to display advertisements or provide other advertising services on iamwire. These third party Advertisers may use techniques other than HTTP cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record demographic and other Information about you, including your activities on or off iamwire. These techniques may be used directly on iamwire. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these techniques, and that browser settings that block conventional cookies may have no effect on such techniques.

Advertisers may use the information collected to display advertisements that are tailored to your interests or background and/or associate such information with your subsequent visits, purchases or other activities on other websites. Advertisers may also share this information with their clients or other third parties.

**iamwire has no responsibility for the technologies, tools or practices of the Advertisers that provide advertising and related services on iamwire**. This Privacy Policy does not cover any collection, use or disclosure of Information by Advertisers who provide advertising and related services on iamwire. These Advertisers’ information gathering practices, including their policies regarding the use of cookies and other tracking technologies, are governed entirely by their own privacy policies, not this one.

iamwire currently may be using one or more of the following Advertisers to provide advertising and related services on iamwire. If you would like to know about their information gathering and privacy practices, please visit the links below

**Analytics Services**

In addition, iamwire uses third party analytics providers and products to obtain, compile and analyze Information (that may include Personally Identifying Information) about how users are using and interacting with iamwire. iamwire may provide Information (including Personally Identifying Information) to these analytics providers for the purpose of obtaining statistics and other information about how users are using and interacting with iamwire. These analytics providers may use tracking techniques other than HTTP cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect or compile this information. These techniques may be used directly on iamwire. iamwire has no responsibility for the technologies, tools or practices of the third parties that providing analytics products and services to iamwire. Please also keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these techniques, and that browser settings that block conventional cookies may have no effect on such techniques.

**Security and Protection of Personally Identifying Information**

We have implemented reasonable security measures and practices in an effort to protect the confidentiality of your Personally Identifying Information (other than Personally Identifying Information that you have elected to disclose to others). However, no security system is impenetrable. It may be possible for third parties to intercept or access information you provide to iamwire. iamwire cannot guarantee the security of your Personally Identifying Information, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to iamwire. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password(s) and computer or device, and to log off when using any shared computer.

**Email or Text Message Communications**

We may contact you by e-mail, text message or other equivalent electronic communications if you access iamwire products or services or register for events, or other content or services provided by iamwire. By visiting or using iamwire content, products or services, or registering for or attending iamwire events, you specifically consent to the receipt of these e-mail or text message communications. If you do not want to receive emails, text messages or other communications from us, please notify us by email at [info{at}iamwire.com](mailto:info@iamwire.com) and include sufficient information for us to identify your account, including your Name, Email Address (or Cellphone Number) and the specifics of your request. If you unsubscribe, iamwire may still contact you via email or text message for administrative purposes or concerning any products, services or events for which you have registered or are using.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

iamwire retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use and disclosure of Information we obtain is subject to the later of: (1) the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such Information is collected or (2) any subsequent Privacy Policy of which you have notice. If we make material changes to the way we collect, use or disclose Personally Identifying Information, we will notify you by posting a clear and prominent announcement on iamwire or through a direct communication. Your continued access to or use of iamwire following notice of material changes to this Privacy Policy shall constitute consent to any amendments and/or modifications. Your use of iamwire is entirely voluntary, and you may discontinue use of iamwire at any time.

**How to Contact Us**

iamwire welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or its implementation. Any such questions or comments should be submitted via email to [info{at}iamwire.com](mailto:info@iamwire.com) or directed to the address below. We will undertake reasonable efforts to resolve or address your concern.

**Corporate Office**

Wirefoot India Technology Private Limited  
SCO – 18, 2nd Floor, Housing Board Complex  
Saraswati Vihar, Near MG Road  
Gurgaon – 122002, Haryana, India  
Phone: 0124-4004961
